// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {

  //#region Table de 6
  "6x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "6x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "6x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "6x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "6x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "6x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "30"
  },
  "6x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "6x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "42"
  },
  "6x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "48"
  },
  "6x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "54"
  },
  "6x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "60"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 6

  //#region Table de 7
  "7x0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "7x1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "7x2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "7x3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "21"
  },
  "7x4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "28"
  },
  "7x5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "35"
  },
  "7x6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "42"
  },
  "7x7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "49"
  },
  "7x8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "56"
  },
  "7x9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "63"
  },
  "7x10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "70"
  },  
  //#endregion Table de 7

  //#region Table de 8
  "8x0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "8x1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "8x2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "8x3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "8x4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "32"
  },
  "8x5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  "8x6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "48"
  },
  "8x7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "56"
  },
  "8x8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "64"
  },
  "8x9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "8x10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "80"
  },  
  //#endregion Table de 8

  //#region Table de 9
  "9x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "9x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "9x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "9x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "27"
  },
  "9x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "9x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "45"
  },
  "9x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "54"
  },
  "9x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "63"
  },
  "9x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "9x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "81"
  },
  "9x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "90"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 9
  
  //#region Table de 10
  "10x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "10x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "10x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  "10x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "30"
  },
  "10x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  "10x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "50"
  },
  "10x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "60"
  },
  "10x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "70"
  },
  "10x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "80"
  },
  "10x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "90"
  },
  "10x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "100"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 10
  
  
};